{
    "subject": "resource/The_Chinese_University_of_Hong_Kong,_Shenzhen",
    "predicate": "ontology/president",
    "object": "resource/Yangsheng_Xu",
    "human_readable": "The president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen is Yangsheng Xu.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9835981726646423,
            "question": "Who is the president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9789801836013794,
            "question": "What is the name of the president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9651237726211548,
            "question": "Name the university where Yangsheng Xu serves as president."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.961523711681366,
            "question": "What is the name of the university located in Shenzhen with Yangsheng Xu as its president?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9387926459312439,
            "question": "Is Yangsheng Xu associated with a university in Hong Kong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9348124861717224,
            "question": "What is Yangsheng Xu's role at The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8967695236206055,
            "question": "In what position does Yangsheng Xu hold at The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8838093280792236,
            "question": "Who leads The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7452229261398315,
            "question": "Where does Yangsheng Xu work as president?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6836678981781006,
            "question": "Which institution does Yangsheng Xu lead?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen is Yangsheng Xu.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4389_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Yangsheng Xu work as president?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4389_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who leads The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4389_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what position does Yangsheng Xu hold at The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4389_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4389_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The output for the query \"The president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen is Yangsheng Xu\" is:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Professor Xu Yangsheng is the President of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen. Therefore, the statement \"The president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen is Yangsheng Xu\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}